So I just got back from Karuizawa.
And I found myself at a barbecue!
I've seen this before... heard of it...
Oh, no...
No, it's an accident...
It's the one we've been talking about.
I'm so glad. Is this the second one?
A series?
Yay, yay! I'm so happy!
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy! I had so much fun! I think my love for meat just overflowed.
Hugs to everyone!
This apron is so sturdy, I feel like I could cook with it on.
I wonder if this is okay...
No? No? If it's not working, just put the ice cream down on the pees.
I should've raised or lowered the tempo a little bit, like a semitone or something.
That'll work, too.
I don't know if I can do it today.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Um... it was like this last time.
Yes, it was.
Today is Toraji's.
Yes, Shrimp & Meat Toraji-san.
I'm here.
It's Toraji-san!
Doodle-doodle-doodle-doodle!
Oh! Ooh.
You guys, you can watch it while you eat your dinner.
Okay, everyone.
Good job today, God hanky.
Okay.
I'm done. I'm in the God Hanky.
I can't, I can't. I'm not in God Hanky anymore.
It's been in there for a long time.
Okay, thank you for your hard work this year.
I'm good, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
I'm good, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
Let's drink. Ginger Elle.
Hey, it's good.
Not one for two, but one for one today.
It's outrageous.
It's glowing.
How extravagant!
I wonder if it's okay to be so extravagant.
Sirloin nigiri sushi is here!
Sirloin nigiri sushi!
2 cans!
They're here! They're here!
Let's put it in the middle!
Here it comes! Ready!
Bon appétit!
What do you want to start with?
Not bread? First.
Bread, indeed. Bread, indeed.
It's so beautiful.
I'm in the tan.
Yes, Tan.
Tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan tan
Tongue in cheek, tongue in cheek, tongue in cheek.
This is delicious.
Tasty tongue? Yes, sir.
Wow.
Oh, hora.
Sounds good!
We eat barbecue all the time.
Hey.
Have we talked about this before?
Yes, we have.
We had yakiniku just recently.
I'm happy.
Shall we eat?
Let's start with the yukke.
Let's start with the yukhoe.
How's the yukke?
I'm having cucumber and apple first.
Oh, vegetables.
Okay.
How is it?
Um, they're crunchy and delicious.Um, crispy and delicious.
That's good.
I'll have some too.
Is it good?
It's good.
Yum! Yum!
Yum!
I'll go with you.
Yum.
Yum!
I'm so happy.
It's a little seared style, isn't it?
Oh, hey, I thought
It was a little overcooked.
It wasn't yet.
It wasn't ready.
It wasn't done yet.
Not yet.
It's our, uh, glue.
That's right.
I hope you guys are watching.
I'm worried about you.
How's it going?
What do you think?
What's going on?
Oh!
What is this? What is this?What is this?
It's my favorite imitation.
Take a guess!
In the comments section
Oh!
The first one!
Yes!
I heard it was the top of the line.
Want some?
Let's eat.
First one.
First round.
Yes! Bon appétit!
Gyuu!
Mmmmmm!
So soft!
Isn't it soft?
Yes!
This summer went so fast, didn't it?
Mm-hm.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Sorry about the timing.
The tour was in the spring for the first time this year, right?
That's when we were able to do it.
So it was kind of like...
I've got a lot of memories from the first half of the year.
What did we do?
Summery stuff.Summery things
Have I done anything summery?
Surprisingly.
We saw fireworks at Icono Joy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I was on the Icono Joy channel.
We had a barbecue and somen noodles floating in the stream.
It was a very summery day when I came here
Soumen-nagashi, Kagoshima is famous for it, right?
Yeah.
There is a place called "Higashi Senbashi
There is a place called "Higashi Senbashi".
You can catch ayu (sweetfish) there.
There is a river next to the place where they serve Somen-nagashi.
You can go ayu fishing there.
You can eat the fish you catch.
Grilled with salt.
They even make it for you.
Nice, summery thing.
Oh, you're here, aren't you?
Somen Noodles in the sink.
Oh, yeah! A machine like a nagashi somen set.
You know, like with Saya and stuff.
Did you get it right?
Yes!
I poured tomatoes down the drain, and there were so many tomatoes!
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Fast.
Tomatoes are sink tomatoes
It's a sink tomato.
But you know what? I want to do it together.
Let's do it together.
We'll all bring tomatoes?
Tomatoes? It's so hard to grab tomatoes.
No!
You're the abalone.
I'm an abalone. I'm an abalone.
That's true.
It's just our reaction.
I'd like to see that.
Okay, everyone.
I'll show you.
It's right here, but...
It's big.
Oh, my God.
You've got it in your hand.
So you're an abalone.
I didn't know abalone shells looked like this.
Noisy color.
Here comes the abalone!
Can you hold it with me?
I'm so excited.
Abalone is amazing.
Oh, wow.Ooh.
Ooh!
Wow.
Cherry blossom viewing parties... they had them all over the place this summer.
They did! So from a distance.
Did you see it? I saw it... once.
It was beautiful. Was it the one you gave me? I don't know!
That's nice. You didn't forget this, did you?
Oh, yeah! Let's eat! Sirloin nigiri.
There's wasabi, too.
Do you like wasabi on your rice? It's hard to decide.
I think I'd like to keep it as is.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
It's amazing.
It's all coming through.
It's good beef.
Wow.
I mean, it's just...
It's so shiny.
Bon appétit!
So much wasabi.
Yeah.
You know, I think meatballs are thin and juicy.
Thick, tender and juicy! Squeeze!
Squeeze!
The one and only!
I'm glad I can do it before that every year. I'm just glad I get to do it every year before that.
The bubbles.
I saw that...
Moeiko was buried at the end.
Did you notice?
I don't know... it was kind of bubbling.
Don't worry, it's organic.
Yes, it's gentle on the skin.
But I was kind of buried, and when I came out of the screen.
I was so surprised.
She was so calm.
I didn't think she was buried like that.
I thought everyone was buried.
Then I saw the video and everything.
Me and Yuka Murayama.
Miyagi's Yuka...
The members with the same number on the other side
I heard that the flowers were pretty much buried, too.
That's why my T-shirt was all pink.
And it was that one, with color?
Yes, yes, yes.
It was gorgeous.
So, yeah.
I, you know, I had red hair for the Equalizer.
It was so pink afterwards.
I thought, "What happened to my hair color?
I'm really sorry.
Yuuka-chan's hair was also very pink. Yuuka-chan and the others were much pinker.
There was a pink girl and a yellow girl.
That's right.
It was my first time doing the foam maneuver.
Go out to the side of the B-station.
There's a platform just outside of there.
Standing platform.
You go up there.
"I'm going to throw bubbles on everybody now.
I was so pumped to go.
I think it was my thing.
It was stuck.
But I hit the button, and it's been there forever.
And now it's firing.
Two sets of fans...
You know, like...
They were standing there like that.
I thought, "Oh, no, no, no, no.
I tried to move it a little bit, but...
There are two rows, right?
You know, this guy here moved it a little bit.
You know, this guy here...
He just shifted here.
I've been hanging here all day.
Sorry.
But you seemed to be having a good time, so I'm glad you're having a good time.
Yeah, it was like a mountain. I felt the same way.
I was right next to Nia and Mitsuki. I was right next to a near actress, Mitsuke-chan.
Mitsuke-chan was probably feeling a little bit the same way.
Just the two of us, like this.
I'm sorry, you mean everyone?
I'm the one who didn't do the bubbles.
I see.
Shiori was on the same stage as me.
I'm bigger than her, so I can vacuum bubbles.
In that case...
Aya.
Suzuki.
What's your name?
We were watching from our home-stay during rehearsal.
We had rehearsal too, so we were outside the mountain.
I was watching you two from above.
Which one was it?
The pupil?
The pupil had a lot of bubbles.
Yes, they were very strong.
And then...
What? That?
I was like, "Am I gonna be okay?
And then I looked the other way and saw Sara's face.
I thought it was just rehearsal.
But then there was a tilt, and Hitomi was getting a lot of bubbles.
It was so exciting!
But Saya's background was kind of cool with bubbles.
That was cute. That was cute.
It was adorable.
I had a lot of water guns.
They all looked like they were going to start spraying.
I was like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah," and then the wind was blowing in my direction, and I was spraying it all over myself.
It was amazing.
That's what happened last year.
I thought, "Okay, I'm going to shoot my first shot," and when I went to shoot it, it didn't go off.
It didn't come out?
It didn't come out.
I just did a bunch of air vacuums.
That's what happened.
Because, you know, you're running under the table a lot faster now.
I'd like to try a stop-and-go race sometime... with you guys.
I'll do it in a sliding style.
I'm going to play Chisuzu Minamiha.
I hope we can do it next year.
I hope we can do it.
After such a summer, it's time for fall.
Thanksgiving in the fall?
Thanksgiving this year.
Is it over?
How was it?
I don't know. We haven't done it yet.
I mean... spoilers.
Well, let's see what you think. Okay, so I'm going to anticipate and I'm going to give you my thoughts now.
Okay.
Let's talk about our Thanksgiving thoughts.
Oh, my God, you guys were...
It was great.
I'm sure you all know that.
What we did was sing in the chorus.
Of course, we won the gold prize!
To win the highest gold medal in the chorus competition.
We took on this chorus.
I never thought that such a performance...
Styling innovation.
I didn't expect that.
And with a production like that...
I don't think there have been many chorus contests like that in Japan.
I don't think there are many in Japan.
That's for sure.
It was a new style.
We flew in the sky and everything.
We flew in the sky.
Everyone was so surprised.
Everyone sang together at the end.
Everyone.
And all the fans joined in.
You've been writing.
That was amazing.
The god of chorus probably dwelled in you.
It was a god episode. A god episode. And then there's the documentary Of Not Equal. It was a god episode, a god episode, and then there's the Documentary of Not Equal.
I thought of this title!
Nyoo! Yay!
The one with hiragana.
The cute one. That was great too.
He said it had a shocking ending.
I never thought it would come to that.
But it's because of that time...
Noemin's history will be written because of that time.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
That was fun. That was fun.
It's amazing.
Can you see it?
It's an amabi.
Look out!
It's impossible.
Cut it with scissors.
I don't know.
It's like three pieces for three pieces.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Crab.
Go for it. You can do it.
Good, good.
It's hot. I need a break.
I'm sorry I didn't go.
But you went to the aquarium, right?
I went to the aquarium. It was so summery.
It was summery. Like a festival.It was summery. Like a festival.
I've never been there before, but it was so beautiful.
There were so many different spaces and themes, you know?
It was really interesting. There were flowers and stuff.
There were so many cute little girls.
I'm going to imitate you tomorrow, right?
I don't know... her cheeks...
There was a girl with soft cheeks... and her cheeks were like hearts.
It was so cute!
Like this.
That's right, that's right. Nanaka did it. I copied her.
I mimicked her movements between the tanks, like this.
You should check it out.
I want you to check it out.
Purr-fectly, purr-fectly, purr-fectly, purr-fectly, purr-fectly...
That's right.
Where do you think your cheeks are coming from?
This is what it looks like when it flies.
It really swims like this.
And there was a goldfish with a very difficult name.
I took a picture of him with just his name.
You don't remember?
I don't remember.
It was something like... savamba-savamba.
I don't know what it was.
Can I see it?
Savamba Savamba.
There it is! There it is! There it is, there it is, there it is.
Sarasatamatasaba.
Just the "sa" and the "b".
It was "sara-satamu-masaba.
That's not quite right.
I wonder when the abalone is ready.
I'm fine.
You want to eat first?
You sure?
Thank you.
Abalone.
Ready!
So soft!
So purr-fect!
She's not Sarasato-Tamasaba.
She's not sara sata mackerel.
Yummy! It's a big one.
It's almost Christmas.
Yes, it's almost Christmas.
I want to have a Christmas party!
I want all the fans to be there!
We've never had a Christmas party, have we?
We have Christmas live shows, but we don't have parties.
We'll exchange presents.
Throwing presents!
Like throwing rice cakes!
Sure, sure, sure.Certainly, certainly, certainly.
Take it!
Mochimaki?
You don't know what mochi maki is?
It's here!
You built a house?
When it's built.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, no! That's embarrassing!
No way!
Is that a local thing?
I guess I just don't know.
Let's do it when we build the house!
Let's do it!
It's been like two months.
A lot.
I'd like to do a lot of things.
If we can do something.
Spend time together... in winter...
And fall.
Next year.
Spring and summer.
So, I've been talking a lot, but...
Oh, abalone!
Isn't it amazing?
After this, we continued to enjoy the barbeque
Let's eat a lot of delicious food and stay healthy!
Let's all stay healthy!Stay healthy!
Stay healthy!
Squeeze!
Hugs! Bye-bye!
Will there be a third installment?
I hope so!